# Joanna Pastcan

(707) 478-5376 timelessmoment05@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/jo37973 github.com/Jo37973

#### **SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS**

Dedicated and efficient full stack developer with skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and responsive web design from the University of Irvine. With each project, I strive to further my knowledge and skills, and engage my audience for an impactful user experience. Additional experience in the field of Education, substitute teaching for over ten years, and ran a photography business for six years. Rounded skills in organization, planning, creativity, and problem-solving. Seeking to further improve full stack developer skills for future clients and employers.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of California, Irvine October 11, 2021- present

• Full Stack Developer

Sonoma State University, Rohnert Park CA August 2005 - May 2009

- BA in Liberal Studies
- Graduated cum laude, overall GPA 3.8
- Preliminary Multiple Subject Teaching Credential

Childbirth International, Online 2013

- Birth Doula Certificate
- Postpartum Doula Certificate

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Substitute Teacher K-12 (Napa Valley Unified School District) February 2009 - 2011, 2017, present

- Substitute in classrooms for K-12 students of up to thirty-five students for all subject areas.
- Apply strategies for effective classroom learning while maintaining classroom rules and discipline to encourage positive behaviors.

• Quickly became a "first-to-call" resource to cover for absent teachers.

Temporary Contract (Alkar Human Resources)
June 9<sup>th</sup>, 2021 – present

- Napa Valley Orthopedic 6/28/21-7/6/21
  - Medical Patient Call Center New Patient Data Entry Customer Service
- Reliable Refrigeration 7/7/21 10/5/21
  - Customer Service Representative
- Wilson Daniels 10/21/21 11/24/21
  - Administrative Office Assistant

Customer Service Representative (Allied Propane Service) July 6, 2017 - November 11, 2017

- Answer incoming calls and assist walk-in customers with their propane needs for their home or business.
- Open and close the daily POS, file, intake and process customer payments. Manage accounts, print and file month-end reports and purchase orders.
- Took initiative to create a spreadsheet to monitor burned/not burned propane tanks and information at properties during the 2017 Napa/Sonoma fires.

•

Birth & Portrait Photographer, Doula (Timeless Moments) August 2010- 2016

- Owned and ran a small photography and doula business
- Birth and Portrait Photography for local clients
- Birth and Postpartum Doula to assist new parents before, during, and after the birth of their child(ren)

Personal Assistant (ELMC, Dr. Bruce and Mary Hopewell) June 2008 – February 2009

- Organize educational and tax accounting business information in Microsoft Word and

  Excel
- Answer phones, record data, schedule meetings and appointments.
- House tasks and running errands.

Business Assistant (Napa Wedding Source, Chris Andrews) June 2000 – May 2005

- Collect and organize data and files into Microsoft Word and Excel.
- Answer phone calls and log all information.
- Schedule meetings and run errands.

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Bootstrap, jQuery
- Microsoft Word
- 80-120 WPM typing
- Lesson planning/implementation of substitute teacher plans

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- B.A. Liberal Arts
- Preliminary Multiple Subject Teaching Credential
- Substitute Teacher Permit (NVUSD)
- Birth and Postpartum Doula Certification
- (Pending completion of UCI Bootcamp:) Full-Stack Web Development Certificate

## **VOLUNTEER**

501st Legion: Golden Gate Garrison

February 2016-present

- Photographer, Handler, and Star Wars Cosplay (Kylo Ren and Shoretrooper)
- Non-profit, charity events for the community

Moon Valley Cul-de-sac Representative

December 2021- present

• Cul-de-sac representative for the members in the Moon Valley Park community